Preliminary Inventory to the George Andrucki Papers WAG.109
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
George Andrucki Papers
1970s-1990s
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Andrucki, George
WAG.109
3.25 Linear Feet (4 boxes)
Box 1-4
Scope and Contents
Correspondence and personal files of George Andrucki, retired Business Agent of Sheet Metal Workers, Local 28.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by George Andrucki, 2001. The accession number associated with this gift is 2002.028.
Andrucki, George
- Inventory
  - Arbitration (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Building Contractors Association: Membership List (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Election Material, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Tom Carlough (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Catholic Social Teaching and the U.S. Economy (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1982-2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Constitutions and By-Laws: Sheet Metal Workers (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Contracts: Sheet Metal Workers, 1950s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Contracts, 1980s-1990s (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Contracts: Local 400, Sheet Metal Workers, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Local 55 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Election Materials (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Elections: Letters and Law (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Elections (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Empire State College: Personal Records (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Empire State College: Personal (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Empire State College (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Empire State College: Personal (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Empire State College: Personal (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Empire State College History: Rosenberg, B. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Employers List: Sheet Metal Workers, Locals 28 & 638 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Ferrari, Robert J. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - History: Steamfitters International Union (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Joint Adjustment Board: Charges, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Labor Day Parade (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Minutes: Sheet Metal Workers, Local 28 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - NLRB 222 No. 110 (Fabrication) Decision, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Newsletter: Local 28 (Ventlines), 1990s (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Peer Counselor (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Petition: Opposition to "B" Local (Sheet Metal, Local 28), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Pension Fund: Charges and Appeals, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Photographs: George Andrucki (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - "Responsible Contractors" Policy, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Safety and Health (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, Local 17: History, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Local 28 of New York: 15th Annual Dinner Dance Booklet (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Local 28 of New York: 16th Annual Dinner Dance Booklet (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Local 28 of New York: 17th Annual Dinner Dance Booklet (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Local 28 of New York: 19th Annual Dinner Dance Booklet (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Local 28 of New York: 21st Annual Dinner Dance Booklet (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Local 28 of New York: 23rd Annual Dinner Dance Booklet (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Local 28 of New York: 24th Annual Dinner Dance Booklet (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Local 28 of New York: 25th Annual Dinner Dance Booklet (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Local 28 of New York: 26th Annual Dinner Dance Booklet (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Local 28 of New York: 27th Annual Dinner Dance Booklet (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Local 28 of New York: 28th Annual Dinner Dance Booklet (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Local 28 of New York: 29th Annual Dinner Dance Booklet (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Local 28 of New York: 30th Annual Dinner Dance Booklet (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Local 28 of New York: 31st Annual Dinner Dance Booklet (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Souvenir Programs, 1977-1978, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Souvenir Programs, 1969, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Souvenir Programs, 1995, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Souvenir Program (75th Anniversary), 1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Souvenir Programs, 1975, 1993, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Souvenir Programs, 1981-1982, 1984, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Souvenir Programs (Tribute to Ed Carlough) (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Souvenir Program, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Souvenir Program, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Souvenir Programs: Empire State College (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Trade Unionism: Essays (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Trial Board Hearing: McBrearty et al vs. Moore, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Trial Board Hearing: McBrearty et al vs. Moore, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Van Arsdale, Harry (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Wagner Labor Archives (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Welfare and Pension Fund (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Handbook: Youth to Youth Program for SMWIA Local Unions (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Handbook: Business Representatives, Sheet Metal Workers (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Handbook: Welfare & Pension Funds, Sheet Metal Workers, Local 28 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook: Business Agent (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Buttons and Badges (Box 4)